# Nutrapong Jariyathanoi

Bangkok, Bangkok City, Thailand



benutrapong@live.com



+66891887999



linkedin.com/in/nutrapong-jariyathanoi-06046149

### **Summary**

First, I started my experience which in hardware configure and server solution.

At the appropriate time, I changed my attention to developed software and network system (inc. Security).

Thus, I've experience in IT field all about 15 years.

(Included 3 years experience of GDPR/PDPA with in the Data Protection Policy and related procedures)

#### Core competencies

- IT Strategy/Plan
- Enterprise Architecture
- Team and Project Management
- BU Continuity Management
- IT/IS Security/Policies
- GDPR/PDPA
- Risk Management/Impact Analysis
- IT Audit
- Network Administrator
- Cloud Solutions
- Disaster Recovery
- Research and Development

Skill

**Business Continuity Management:** 

ISO 22301 ~ ISO/IEC 27001 ~ BS 25999 ~ COBIT 5 ~ ITIL ~ CMMI

Info. Security/Management:

ISO/IEC 27002 ~ ISO/IEC 17799 ~ ISO/IEC 29100 ~ ISO/IEC 27701 ~ ISO/IEC 27017

OS:

Windows 11/10/8/7/XP/NT/ME/98/MS

Server 2000/2003/2003R2/2008R2/2012 ~ Linux ~ Mac OS X ~ Unix ~ Mobile

Mail System:

Lotus Domino Server/Administrator 8.5.3, 6.5 ~ Lotus Note 8.5.3, 6.5 ~ Outlook 97, XP, 2010, 2013 ~ Mozilla

Thunderbird 2.0-17.0.8

Language:

PowerBuilder ~ Visual Basic ~ C/C++ ~ JAVA ~ J2ME ~ HTML ~ PHP ~ Python

Application:

G Suite ~ MS Dynamics Great Plains ~ Express

Scripting:

JavaScript/Ajax ~ Shell ~ .Net

DB/Server:

Oracle ~ SQLServer ~ MySQL ~ ACCESS ~ Fox Pro

Cloud system:

Openstack, VMWare vSphere Virtualization: Linux KVM, MS Hyper-V

### **Experience**



### IT Manager/DPO

Sub Sri Thai Public Co., Ltd.

Aug 2017 - Feb 2022 (4 years 7 months)

- Oversee the Management of Company's Business Continuity Plans and Management; ICT Policy, Rules, Security and Standards; Configuration; And Disaster Recovery; Implement and Apply by use the Enterprise Solutions.
- Explore and Assess the Feasibility of New and Emerging Technologies to Provide Operational Efficiencies that Support the Company's Short and Long Terms IT Strategy; for an Investment in Technology Infrastructure and Application on Cloud Solutions to Enhance the Achievement of the Company's Goals and Objectives.
- · Manage Information Technology Initiatives; including Costs, Timing, Risk Management, and Resource Management of IT Project Delivery;
- Review and Prioritise Infrastructure Investments and Recommend Changes to Standards in Support of Evolving Business Needs and Technologies.
- Develop, Oversee, and Execute the Annual Departmental Budget; while finding Efficiencies through Continuous Process Improvement:
- Demonstrate to Stakeholders and Decision-Makers the Business Opportunities of Cross-Departmental Technological Investments and Governance.
- Direct Department Staff; including Recruitment, Motivation, Coaching and Training, Performance Management, Organizational Structure, and Career Development;
- Review Selection of Hardware and Software, and Maintain Vendor Relationships and Contracts.
- Participate in All ICT Audits Process.Review the Data Protection Policy and related procedures
- Provide consultation on regulatory and legal compliance
- Provide assistance in the integration and implementation of PDPA compliance throughout the internal processes and services
- Ensure that consent, privacy notice, data subject right response, and data breach handling meet the PDPA requirements
- Assistance in identifying and mitigation of PDPA risks including Data Protection Impact Assessment
- Conduct PDPA compliance and risk assessments including conduct Data Protection Impact Assessment.
- Assist business units to comply with the PDPA.



### Digital strategy consultant

Thai Media Fund

Jan 2018 - Sep 2020 (2 years 9 months)

- · Providing advice about the digital transformation process and operational capabilities by choosing and ensuring the right architecture and functionality suitable to the business need including the digitization, process automation and knowledge management.
- Conduct and analyses the business-related organizations, operating models, processes, applications and infrastructure and formulate recommendations and roadmaps to improve business-functions.
- Involvement in business's digital transformation process for the conceptualization and implementation of advanced technological solutions to complex problems that require specific and in-depth knowledge respondent to the business's need, in the following areas: - Implementation of specialist technologies:

architecture definition, Big Data, solutions development and tool implementation. - IT strategy and governance: strategic IT plans, IT servicing, Project Management Office (PMO), transformation, organization and efficiency. - Risk and regulatory management: cybersecurity, data quality and data governance.

# Chief System Engineer

The Thailand Research Fund

Oct 2008 - Aug 2017 (8 years 11 months)

- Developed organization's ICT Strategy, Policies and Procedures. Including Business continuity management, Change Management, Incident Management, Risk Management, Problem Escalation and Service Level Agreements.
- Worked regularly with CIO to help align technology with the current business objective goals. Met with CEO to assure alignment of technology initiatives and long term business strategies.
- Manage the success of the project within the agreed upon project scope, deliverables, plans and milestones by documents with utilizing the Gantt Chart, Network Logic and Work Breakdown Structure; Independently initiate, lead, plan, implement, and coordinate activities of simple in low-risk projects; Dealing with moderately complex considerations of risk and impact on systems and multiple interfaces and dependencies to other Agency systems; Building reclamation and preparation, service redundancies, design consultation, documentation and portfolio management; Clearly present information and interpret complex information, coaching, developing and mentoring staff movement enabling.
- Assumed the role of Information Security Officer to provide guidance on compliance and security, including ISO 22301:2012, ISO/IEC 27001, BS 25999 and ITIL. Developed InfoSec architecture and strategy before creating separate role and staffing the InfoSec function.
- Overviewed the Security Authorization process of ICT systems, and verified and validated that the systems meet specified security requirements and conform to the Agency and Federal policies (Ministry of Information and Communication Technology), regulations, standards and guidelines outlined in ISO/IEC 27002, ISO/IEC 17799:2005, etc.
- Decide and evaluated new or enhanced technical and operational services and provided guidance on the establishment of security requirements and standards. Monitored trends in technology, and performed systems security analyses and recommended strategies for improving or enhancing system security.

# Programmer

The Thailand Research Fund Regional Office

Jul 2007 - Jul 2008 (1 year 1 month)

- Develop, Design, Maintenance computers, network & in-house software system.
- Responsible for standard automatic monitoring and managed corporate systems and support services (Assisted networking, software & hardware administrator in solving network, software & hardware problem).
- Automated systems monitoring tasks using standard monitoring tools.
- Worked as a team member for develop web application, in-house programs to connect and transfer data between Applications and databases. (PowerBuilder, Oracle, SQL, MS Access)

# Programmer and IT Administrator

Hollywood International Ltd.

Jun 2006 - Mar 2007 (10 months)

- Develop programs and Created modules programs to connect and transfer data between Applications and SQL databases (Visual basic 6.0, FoxPro, SQL, MS Access).
- Maintenance computers, network & accounting software system in corporation (MS Dynamics Great Plains, Express 5).
- Assisted network, software & hardware admin in solving network, software & hardware problem.

### Education



### Kasetsart University

Master of Science Program in Information Technology, Information Technology 2012 - 2014

Member of the High Performance Computing & Network Computing Center (HPCNC) Laboratory, Department of Computer Engineering, Faculty of Engineering,

### Project:

The Development of a Disaster Recovery Software using Cloud Technology.

#### Research:

Cloud, Disaster Recovery, Virtualization, Open Source.

# Mae Fah Luang University

Bachelor of Science (Computer Science), Computer Science 2002 - 2006

- Leader of School of Information Technology's Tutor Team in the following Subjects: Programming, Math, Operating systems, etc.
- Research Assistant: Assisted IT lecturers in searching for research information.

### **Licenses & Certifications**

- Configuring Windows 8 ISONET CO., LTD.
- **Business Continuity Management Master class 2013** National Electronics and Computer Technology Center (NECTEC)
- Lotus Notes Basic Admin & Lotus Notes Application Training Zenithcomp Co., Ltd.
- PowerBuilder 12.0 Boot Camp. SSC Integration Co., Ltd.
- **MCSA: Windows 8** Microsoft
- International Cloud Workshop Foundation Cloud Security Alliance Thailand Chapter

Google Certified Associate - G Suite Administrator - Google Issued Dec 2016 - Expires Aug 2018 PR000023

- ICT Security The Digital Economy Promotion Agency
- Management 3.0 Foundations Workshop Wu-Wei Research Institute
- Data Protection ICDL Asia
  TH0000008986
- Microsoft Certified: Azure Fundamentals Microsoft 1001-5090
- Microsoft Certified: Power Platform Fundamentals Microsoft 1015-0249
- Microsoft Certified: Azure Data Fundamentals Microsoft 1034-0675
- Microsoft Certified: Azure Al Fundamentals Microsoft 1043-2931
- Microsoft Certified: Identity and Access Administrator Associate Microsoft Issued Jan 2022 - Expires Jan 2023 1104-8865
- Microsoft Certified: Information Protection Administrator Associate Microsoft Issued Jan 2022 - Expires Jan 2023 I111-2274
- Microsoft Certified: Security, Compliance, and Identity Fundamentals Microsoft 1112-4582

### **Skills**

Network Administration • Network Engineering • Lotus Notes • Lotus Domino • PowerBuilder • Servers • Windows 7 • System Administration • Disaster Recovery • Windows 8